Guide to the Stephen S. Fuller papers, 1932, 1956-2016
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 3: Washington, D.C., 1932, 1956-2016 (Boxes 14-37)
  - "The Impact of the Proposed Union Market on the District of Columbia Economy", June 2013 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - "The Impact of the 2013 Washington Auto Show on the District of Columbia Economy", May 2013 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Clippings from The Washington Business Journal, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - "The Roadmap for the Washington region's Future Economy", December 2015 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Report on the annual operating costs of Dominion Electric, October 2015 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Reports on the economic impact of AZA-accredited Zoos and Aquariums in Washington, D.C., January 2015 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Proposed International Spy Museum at L'Enfant Plaza on the District of Columbia", June 4, 2015 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Reports on welfare reform in Washington, D.C., 2009 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - National Capital Planning Commission conference documents, November 8, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Center for Regional Analysis reports on improving Washington's global competitiveness, September 22, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Center for Regional Analysis report on corporate activity in the Washington, D.C. area, August 19, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Presentation on the Economic Recovery Act of Washington, D.C., June 25, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Report supporting tax cuts in Washington, D.C., circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - "What Do We Know About the Effect of Taxes on Economic Development?" by Stephen T. Mark, et al, June 2, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Tax Commission staff report on the relationship between Washington, D.C. and the government, circa 2000 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - "Reassessing the District of Columbia's Financial Future" by McKinsey and Company, January 22, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - "The Southwest Washington Urban Renewal Program" by Jule Burland and Beth Coplan, April 17, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Anacostia Waterfront Initiative fold-out publication, March 2001 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Capital Columns Volume 1, Issue 4, circa 2002 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the economic impact of Washington area airports, October 1991-March 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Report on the strategy for the revitalization of the Waterside Mall, March 1998 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - "Crystal City Future City" by Bezabih Getachew, April 24, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Reports on community development in Washington, D.C., circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - "Evaluating Community Development: A Case Study of Washington, D.C." by Lindley R. Higgins, May 3, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Torpedo Factory pamphlets, July 1978 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Report on growth and transportation in Washington, D.C., June 1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Census data for Washington, D.C., 1990 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Special report on the 1990 census, July 1992 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Reports on the Washington, D.C. economy, February-March 1979 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Growth trends in Washington, D.C., 1995-2015 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Transportation future for the Washington region, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - United States International Cultural and Trade Center summary, June 1983 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Greater Washington Research Center reports on technology in Washington, D.C., 1985-1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Co.", December 1980 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Emergency preparedness in Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Belmont/Devilliers Neighborhood Design Study", March 1979 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "The Washington Metropolitan Area's Future: 2035", July 1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Environmental impact study on Washington, D.C., October 1993 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "The Lower-Wage Recovery in the Higher-Wage Economy of the Washington, D.C. Area" by Lokeshi Dani, October 2013 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "The Economies of Washington, D.C. and the Downtown Business Improvement District", April 3, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - "The Economic Impact of the Proposed 800-Seat Shakespeare Theatre for Washington, D.C.", circa 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "The Impact of the Entertainment Industry on the Economies of the District of Columbia and Its Mid-City District", September 2007 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "The Impact of the Hospitality Industry on the Metropolitan Washington Economy", March 1995-September 1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Corcoran Gallery Expansion", January 2004 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impacts of the Proposed Duke Street Connector Alternatives", March 27, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - "Impact of Metrorail on the Metropolitan Washington Economy", July 1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Report on revenue impacts and youth sports, November 2014 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - "Calculating the Fiscal impact of Energy Price Changes Resulting from Implementing the Kyoto Protocol", April 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - "The Kyoto Protocol: Troubling Questions for American Seniors", March 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of Increased Energy Costs on City Governments", November 5, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - "Impact of Intraurban Tax Differentials on Business and Residential Location in the Washington Area", 1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - "Tax Differentials as Business Location Determinants", 1978 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - "Technical Aspects of the District's Tax System", December 1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - "The Changing Economy of the Washington Area", December 1983 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - "The District of Columbia's Changing Economy and its Future Growth Opportunities", September 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - "The Structure and Performance of the District of Columbia's Economy", September 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - "Coincident and Leading Indicators" parts 1-3, March-May 2000 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - "Coincident and Leading Indicators" parts 4-6, June-August 2000 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal impacts of the World Bank Group on Washington, D.C.", April 2002 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Presentation on the impact of terrorism on the Washington, D.C. economy, October 10, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of the Federal Government on the District of Columbia", August 2003 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "Washington, D.C.'s Technology Industry", circa 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Reports on the impact of biomedical research on local economies, September 2003 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - "The Impact of the Crushed Stone, Sand and Gravel Industry on the U.S. Economy", 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - "The Potential Impact of a Hotel Workers Strike on the District of Columbia", January 24, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Washington, D.C. Chamber of Commerce presentation on education, November 15, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - "Washington Metropolitan Area Mid-Year Economic Review and Forecast", September 2006 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - "An Evaluation of Research on the Performance of Loans with Down Payment Assistance", August 31, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - "The National Capital Region's Economy: International Strengths and Links to China", September 2006 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Research paper on The U.S. Army Women's Foundation, circa 2000 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - "A Comprehensive Analysis of Non-Profit Down Payment Assistance", June 2007 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impacts of the Proposed Capitol Square Hotel on the District of Columbia', November 2008 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - "The Impact of Community Bridge, Inc. on the District of Columbia Economy", August 2009 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - "The Economic Impact of the Dow Chemical/Rohm and Haas Merger", August 2009 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of CAPCO-Funded Companies on the District of Columbia", November 2009 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - "The Washington Metropolitan Area 2030 Economic Outlook: Standard Forecast", March 2009 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - "The Future of the Washington Area Economy", September 2009 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Report on the Washington Metropolitan Area Economy, April 2010 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Report on Alexandria's waterfront economic contribution, December 2010 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - "The Fiscal impact of The Haven at Celebrate Virginia on the City of Fredericksburg", March 1, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - "Federal Purchases in Greater Washington", December 1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - "Federal Purchases in the Washington Metropolitan Area", November 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - "Federal Purchases in Greater Washington: Fiscal Year 1989", April 1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Report on federal contracts in the Washington, D.C. area, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Regional Science Association international meeting notes, November 14, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - "Uses of the future in Planning Education: Washington, D.C.", October 5, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Report on the economic performance of Washington, D.C., June 2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - "Planning for the Downtown of Tomorrow", circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - "Regional Economic Independence: The Washington/Baltimore Common Market", November 1, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - "Urban Design for Commercial Revitalization", circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - "The Internationalization of the Washington, D.C. Area Economy", circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Publication about methods of evaluating urban land use, circa 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - "The Washington Area Economy" Resilience and Recovery", January 2003 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Reports on the economic impacts of cultural facilities on local economies, November 2006 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Eighth annual conference on global change and the Washington, D.C. economy, January 2011 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Shifts in the Washington area economy (1 of 2), circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Shifts in the Washington area economy (2 of 2), circa 1980 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - The economic impact of auto shows on the District of Columbia, August 1998-May 2013 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Washington Flyer magazine articles, March 1992-October 1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - "The Changing Sectoral and Geographic Structure of the Washington Area's Economy", 1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Economic study of the National Capital Region, June 30, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - The 2030 Group internal publication, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Woodrow Wilson Bridge project documents, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Reports on growth patterns in Washington, D.C., December 1985-September 2009 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Reports on local businesses and non-profits in Washington, D.C., November 1981-June 1997 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - National Capital Planning Commission publications, August 1992-February 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - "A Social Study of the District of Columbia", 1932 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Economic household reports, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - SMSA Multipliers for Washington, D.C., circa 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Publications authored by Ralph R. Widner, February-October 1968 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 2006 Regional Economic Projections Series, November 2006 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - 2008 Regional Economic Projections Series, November 2008 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Economic analysis of the Baltimore-Washington common market (1 of 2), August 1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Economic analysis of the Baltimore-Washington common market (2 of 2), May 1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - "A Brief History of the L'Enfant Center of the National Capital", September 1996 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Montgomery County Planning Department market analysis, May 11, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Economic impact of arts and culture on Washington, D.C., 1986-2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Report on Washington, D.C. leisure trends, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - "Imagine a Greater Washington" by Bruce Adams, October 2, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Publications about telecommunications and economic planning, circa 1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - The Warner Theatre Project, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - 2050 Study, circa 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Skyland Shopping Center design plan, March 1, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - "The People of the District of Columbia", circa 1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Heights neighborhood planning workshop, circa 1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter of the District of Columbia Chamber of Commence, November 1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Report on tax rates in Washington, D.C., August 2008 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Services for women in Washington, D.C., May 27, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Magazine articles about the Washington, D.C. economy, 2009-2011 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Series 4: Reports from outside the Washington, D.C. region, 1959-2012 (Boxes 37-45)
  This series includes economic reports, enviromental reports, testimonies, and planning documents.
  - "The Plan For The Restructuring of Daqing's Economy"-Revised Draft (1 of 2), March 21, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - "The Plan For The Restructuring of Daqing's Economy"-Revised Draft (2 of 2), March 21, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - "Economic and Fiscal Impact Study of Siting a State Office Building in Fresno, California", May 2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Harvest Hills Community on Jefferson County, West Virginia", August 2001 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - "A Proposed Economic Development Strategy for Graciosa, The Azores", circa 2000 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Testimonies presented by Stephen S. Fuller (1 of 3), 1984-1999 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Testimonies presented by Stephen S. Fuller (2 of 3), 2001-2007 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Testimonies presented by Stephen S. Fuller (3 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "The Economic Impact of the CAA Men's Basketball Championship at Alternative Sites", December 2009 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - "The Economic Impact of Spending for Operations and Construction by AZA-Accredited Zoos and Aquariums", March 2011 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Report on a new major airport for the New Jersey-New York metropolitan area, December 14, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Thesis on Space Use Analysis for the Central Business District of Memphis, Tennessee, August 1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "The Appalachian Experiment: Growth or Development", September 1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Economic development plan for Pensacola, Florida, December 1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Economic development plan for San Juan, Texas, February 1977 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Economic development plan for Detroit Lakes, Minnesota, October 1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Economic development plans for Portugal, June-September 1999 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Report on economic trends in Palm Beach County, Florida, October 2006 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of CAPCO-Funded Companies on the State of New York", April 2010 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - "Current Economic Conditions and Near-Term Outlook for the City of Galveston and Galveston County", October 2010 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Strategies for Revitalizing the Economies of the City of Galveston and Galveston County", November 2010 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Economic development strategies for European cities, 1999-2003 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - "The Impact of the Proposed Gaming Resort and Spa on the Economy of Adams County, PA", December 2005 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - "Planning and Developing Australia", 1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Report on the Detroit regional economy by Ellen D. Harpel, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Appalachian regional commission report, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - "Subregional Development Strategy Central Appalachia", April 1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - "Oral History Project Appalachian Regional Commission", circa 1985 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Coles Hill Uranium Project reports (1 of 2), August 2010-November 2011 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Coles Hill Uranium Project reports (2 of 2), December 2011-September 2012 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission publications, 1970-1985 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission evaluation studies (1 of 3), December 1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission evaluation studies (2 of 3), December 1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Appalachian Regional Commission evaluation studies (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - "A Public Investment Program for the Development of Central Appalachia", circa 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Dangerfield Island environmental assessment, May 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - "Finding the Optimum Site for Disney's America", January 14, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 3)